<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile (H1D023089)</string>
    <string name="club_name">Vfl Wolfsburg</string>
    <string name="club_history">Club History</string>
    <string name="desc_club">VfL Wolfsburg (commonly known as Wolfsburg) is a German professional football club based in Wolfsburg, Lower Saxony. Founded on 12 September 1945, the club enjoys the support and backing of the conglomerate Volkswagen Group, which is also headquartered in the city.
 Wolfsburg plays its home matches at the Volkswagen Arena and achieved a landmark success by winning the Bundesliga title for the first time in the 2008-09 season.</string>
    <string name="head_coach">Head Coach</string>
    <string name="squad">Team Squad</string>
    <string name="desc_history">VfL Wolfsburg was founded on September 12, 1945, in the aftermath of World War II, as part of the efforts to rebuild community life in the city of Wolfsburg, which itself was a relatively new city established around the Volkswagen factory. The club began as a general sports association for the factory’s workers and soon formed a football team that would eventually become the centerpiece of the organization. In its earliest years, the team played in local amateur leagues, gradually developing a following among factory employees and the surrounding community. \n\n
    During the 1950s and 1960s, Wolfsburg remained largely an amateur or semi-professional side, playing in regional competitions. The club benefited from the steady financial and organizational support of Volkswagen, though it was still far from being considered a major footballing power. The team occasionally flirted with higher-level competition but often found itself limited by the small size of its fan base and the dominance of more established clubs in Lower Saxony, such as Eintracht Braunschweig and Hannover 96. \n\n
    The 1970s and 1980s were a period of slow but steady development for the club. Wolfsburg began to establish itself as a competitive team in the lower divisions of German football. The construction of better facilities and the continuous involvement of Volkswagen ensured that the club remained stable even when results on the pitch were inconsistent. By the late 1980s, VfL Wolfsburg was seen as a well-managed club with the ambition to reach professional football. \n\n
    In 1992, Wolfsburg earned promotion to the 2. Bundesliga for the first time in its history, marking a turning point in the club’s fortunes. The step up to the second tier of German football brought new visibility and professional structure. The club started to invest more seriously in player development and infrastructure, while Volkswagen increased its financial commitment, recognizing the potential marketing value of a successful football club representing the company’s hometown. \n\n
    The 1997–98 season was a historic one for VfL Wolfsburg. Under coach Wolfgang Wolf, the team achieved promotion to the Bundesliga for the first time ever. This achievement marked the beginning of Wolfsburg’s rise to prominence in German football. Their debut Bundesliga campaign in 1998–99 exceeded expectations, as the team managed to stay up comfortably and even challenge for European qualification in the following seasons. \n\n
    Throughout the 2000s, Wolfsburg became a consistent presence in the Bundesliga. Volkswagen’s continued support allowed the club to attract higher-quality players and invest in modern facilities, including the construction of the Volkswagen Arena, which opened in 2002. The club began to develop a stronger identity and fan base, transitioning from a “factory team” into a professional football club capable of competing with Germany’s traditional powers. \n\n
    The pinnacle of VfL Wolfsburg’s success came in the 2008–09 season under manager Felix Magath. Led by an explosive attacking trio of Edin Džeko, Grafite, and Zvjezdan Misimović, Wolfsburg stunned the football world by winning their first-ever Bundesliga title. The team’s dynamic, high-scoring style captured the imagination of fans and established Wolfsburg as a legitimate force in German football. Grafite and Džeko were particularly prolific, combining for an astonishing 54 league goals. \n\n
    In the years that followed, Wolfsburg maintained its status as a top-tier club. The team participated in the UEFA Champions League multiple times and reached the quarterfinals of the competition in 2016, where they famously defeated Real Madrid 2–0 in the first leg before being eliminated in the return match. The club also won the DFB-Pokal (German Cup) in 2015 and the DFL-Supercup the same year, solidifying its reputation as one of Germany’s most competitive sides outside the traditional giants like Bayern Munich and Borussia Dortmund. \n\n
    Recent years have seen Wolfsburg focus on balancing financial sustainability with on-field competitiveness. The club has placed a strong emphasis on youth development and data-driven management, aiming to build a team that can regularly compete in European competitions without overspending. While performances have fluctuated, Wolfsburg has remained a respected name in the Bundesliga, known for its modern facilities, efficient management, and consistent presence in the upper half of the table. \n\n
    Today, VfL Wolfsburg represents not only a successful football club but also a symbol of the city’s close connection to Volkswagen and its workers. From its humble postwar beginnings to Bundesliga champions, the club’s story reflects resilience, ambition, and the transformative power of sport within a community built around industry and innovation. \n\n</string>

</resources>